I'm going to show you how make a drink called a Detroit Daisy.
We're going to start off with our ice.
Pour this into your glass just about half way.
Like so.
Then we are going to add to this one ounce of dark rum.
There we go.
Next were going to do a few really good squeezes of lime juice.
One,two, three,one more, four.
It's going to be a very lime-y sort of drink, I guess.
Go ahead and shake that up.
Your going to pour this into a rocks glass.
Just like so.
Last but not least.
We are going to pour in just a little splash of grenadine.
That's going to sink to the bottom.
So, you are going to take your stirry straw and give it a stir.
It's going to be nice and pretty.
You can garnish this with a maraschino cherry.
Just drop that right in there.
There you have it.
A Detroit Daisy.
Cheers.